there's definitely generational
difference with the global warming
that's like my daughter a whole
different feeling about there's a warm
day in winter here a little while ago
it's like last year she was seven and
she came home from school
scared talking about global warming
she's said she was scared by a warm
winter day when I was a kid we enjoyed a
warm winter day it was fun because we
didn't see it as a symptom of impending
doom
so we enjoyed it the same way you would
enjoy sudden weight loss until you find
out it's an intestinal parasite
who fun
and actually it was a lot worse I don't
know if you know that if you're not old
enough to remember the environment was
actually much worse for a while we made
progress we should take be happy about
that a lot of the air way worse way way
worse it was so bad the environment was
so bad we noticed it us the scientists
didn't have to tell us there was a
problem you know like what global
warming would you notice that on your
own really if you live by a glacier yes
you would you'd look out your window and
say well we've got a yard now full of
boulders when did that happen
but like global warming the ocean it
used to go up like a little under two
millimeters now it's going up about
almost four millimeters a year but
really would you notice on your own that
change in depths when you went to the
beach would you go to his the ocean
seemed a little deeper to you this
year's oozing deeper if you notice that
yeah and it's a bit more acidic did you
taste it senior isn't it more acid II
think you're right i think this beach
could use a couple tablespoons of baking
powder
she would notice where as it was so bad
it's so nasty
we didn't need a scientist to tell us in
the 70s that there's a problem when in
1973 the Cuyahoga River in Ohio burst
into flames should I mean any idiot
knows there's a problem when there's a
flammable River
doesn't need to be a scientist you don't
even need a GED for that probably some
junior high dropout down smoking by the
river because it was good for you and he
like threw the button the river and also
go that is not supposed to do that
I'm not a scientist but I'm pretty sure
that suppose distinguished with
cigarette it is this is current
spreading like a son of a gun yeah
call the fire department but tell them
to check their water to see we might
have had as a pair of dickham shift here
women River
and I feel bad for the scientists in a
way because they have to try to
communicate this stuff to us to guy like
me for years I thought I well why can't
you explain it to me
many people explained it to me and
they're like bent we can you're too
stupid what do you mean I'm sure we
remember earlier how you didn't take
math that's problem you don't get it and
then they have to try to not only point
out something you wouldn't notice it
make you worried about it and they're
not always the best at marketing global
warming warn't bad word if you want to
mobilize people don't put warm in the
title
well no worm will it also be toasty but
warm is at worst inconvenient they're
worse like dang it my KitKat melted
completely wrapper doll the contest
instructions covered with chocolate
I have to lick off this wrapper to see
if I'm a winner
[Music]
worms not scary now in the 70s bad
problem genius marketing whoever came of
this great idea to mobilize people
what's scarier global warming acid rain
don't get your attention acid will be
raining out of the sky
you want all the information in detail
so what kind of acid holy cow what kind
of acid like sulphuric battery acid what
I do do I pull my car in the garage that
kind of acid where's my hippy dippy
neighbor gonna run outside with this
mouth open
[Applause]
this is part of your a problem
that'll get your attention anybody's
attention acid rain that's that's that
is crazy
that's even Old Testament crazy
even the Old Testament God would like
ease up with you know what Moses let's
hold off on the acid rain
second thought let's hold off on the
acid rain but let's see how they respond
after we kill all their firstborn hey
did you know that Drybar comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch save and share clips and watch my
whole special